Downloaded @ subs4free.club
My name is Maurice.
I'm French.
I haven't been here
in New York for long.
In Brooklyn.
I left France, but if I
talk to you in English,
it's because the director asked me to.
I don't really talk much.
I won't talk much.
My name is Maurice.
I don't really exist.
I'm just an image on the screen.
People don't like that.
They don't like it.
Is it ok for you?
Yeah, sure it's huge.
Yeah, do you like the wall?
It's interesting.
I just put it in.
I'm not quite sure about
it, but I think I like it.
But make yourself at home.
Come on, coat off, hat off, relax.
Lie on the bed, take a
nap, light your candles.
If you need anything
I'll be in the kitchen.
Ok.
See you in a little bit.
Thank you.
- So if I give you a room,
and maybe you can help
do dishes, or help clean just
a little bit around the house,
or even downstairs in the bar.
Do you think you could do that?
Yeah sure.
Yeah?
Hello darling.
Hey.
This is Maurice.
New baby.
Nice find.
Thanks.
- All right babe, we
gotta talk about John.
You know, I love him,
I know he's your friend,
but he's pocketing money.
I don't trust him.
He's gotta go, ok?
So I'm gonna have to do it.
What's your name again?
Maurice.
Here.
What is this?
Candles.
Come on, let's deal with John, fuck.
- All right, all right,
come on, we gotta go.
We gotta go talk to him.
I'll show you the bar and what to do.
Ok.
- You can meet the
people who work there.
They're nice, they'll like you.
- Go ahead and grab a mop
from the closet over there,
and give the floor a good once-over,
and then after that you can
help me take down the rest
of these chairs, and after
that you can probably go see Kim
downstairs in the basement.
She's probably gonna have a
lot of work for you tonight too.
It's Tuesday so it's probably
not gonna be that busy,
you know, I mean it's
gonna be pretty quiet,
but the main thing is to just
make sure everything's tidy,
clean, make sure everybody's
drinks are refilled,
their waters, and make sure
you wipe down the tables.
Right?
That's important.
Welcome to Bushwick burlesque,
scary bear's bawdy birthday ball,
is that what it said on the Internet?
I think so, something like that.
Exuberance both.
We are celebrating the
birthday of our own peddler
of exuberant
both...
that's me.
Mr scary bear.
- Thanks friends,
family, whores, sluts,
general acquaintances,
and people off the street.
Thank you so much for coming.
- Baby, you gonna
come say, "goodnight?"
- Betty.
- - Hi.
Goodnight.
Night.
How's your room?
It'll do fine.
- Good?
- Yeah.
All right.
Sleep well.
See you.
Bye.
They're stuck.
The eggs?
Mm-hmm.
They're stuck in the pack.
Look.
It's true.
You could just pour it in there.
Do you need me to do anything?
I feel bad just sitting.
No, it's fine.
You're so good to us.
Hello!
How are you?
- Good good good, I brought
croissants for the French boy.
Wow, special treatment.
So help yourself.
Hi babe how are you?
Oh good, how are you?
What are you making?
- Good to see you.
- You too.
So I got a couple of chocolate,
and a couple of I think almond.
Ooh, for you.
Do you have a mug?
Mmm, do you want?
How was it last night?
I didn't work last night,
but I heard it's pretty shitty.
Who played last night?
- It was a DJ, I think
it was David or something,
I don't remember.
New?
- No an old one
we used but...
- we haven't used
him in a while though.
We should start using him more.
Why did we stop?
- It just gets expensive
after a while, you know?
If they're not gonna
bring people, it's like,
why spend that much money, you know?
And you, how was your night?
It was good, good, yeah.
How are your eggs?
Oh, um, they're good, yeah.
- They're good?
- They're what?
Good or cold?
Yeah tell us more about yourself.
Yeah when's your birthday?
We need to know everything.
Yeah, are you a virgin?
Did you run away?
Like your parents?
I don't know.
- Who do you like more,
your mom or your dad?
- Mom.
- - Mom?
Makes sense.
You look really pretty like this.
And I'm not usually?
You're an asshole.
This job's kind of stupid.
But we make a lot of fucking money.
So how was your first day?
Hmm?
How was your first day?
Washing dishes, what about you?
It's good, I'm tired.
Oh I see.
You see the show at all?
Yeah, yeah I did.
It was cool, well
it's strange, but cool.
Yeah?
Did you do all these?
Yeah I did.
Ok, well I'll see you tomorrow.
See you.
You did very well today at the bar.
Well thank you.
No thank you.
You see him?
Yeah he did all right.
She gives you no love.
You did very well.
Thanks.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Would you keep us company tonight?
- Oh, yeah.
- - Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I think that's a good idea.
- You have to take your
underwear off though.
Really?
- It's the rule.
- Ok.
Those are the rules.
Ok.
So shy all the time, why?
I know, so nervous.
Is it something to do with that?
Yes it totally is that.
Wow, I'm impressed baby.
I choose wow, come on Kim.
You should behave.
You should know me better than that.
- You have to behave, we're
not having sex with you.
- All right.
- So you know.
- Again, she's rough,
more mature, but come on.
- Good night baby.
- Night.
- You know this is the
only bathroom here right?
Ah yeah, sorry.
- That's the problem
with you teenagers,
you're either dirty or you
take showers for an hour.
Is it filming?
- Yeah it's filming man,
of course it's filming.
Look at my baby.
Look at the baby.
Baby needs to get clean,
takes an hour long shower.
Baby's gotta get clean.
Good job mommy.
Of course.
Drop the soap.
Just for fun purposes.
Oh fuck girl, it's all getting wet no?
No this thing can go under the water.
- No fuck you, you're
gonna break my phone.
No it can go under the water.
- Fuck you, it's going
black, it's gonna...
oh fuck!
You fucking broke my phone.
Oh, you can get a new one.
You broke it, what the hell?
You know what, it's the case.
No, that is not ok!
- Ok, that's the
reception is over here.
Ok, this is the clothes for
sale for people came to the gym.
This is the punching bag over here,
and those weights you
can have here every day,
and lift weight for the gym.
- One, two, three.
- Ok.
One, two, three, yes?
One, two, three.
Uppercut, yes.
One, two, three, yes very good.
Very good, very good, yes.
Ok, one, two, yes.
And left, right.
- Don't use too
much power. - - Ok.
Don't use too much power.
Yes, left, right, uppercut, yes.
Left, right, uppercut.
- Is that a
bed? - - Yep.
Oh man, why you wanna sleep here?
I don't want to sleep here,
but I left my keys at my apartment,
and my roommate's mad at me,
so this is kinda the only choice.
So bad.
It's not so bad, I've done it before.
Actually pretty comfortable.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah.
- This?
Oh man, I would not sleep on this.
Well I don't really have a choice.
- Maybe if you want, you
could spend a night upstairs.
Where?
My room.
In your room?
Only for a night.
Ok.
Your ceiling's falling down.
Yep.
Doesn't matter.
Night.
Goodnight.
No, I understand what you're saying,
I understand why you're doing it,
I'm just really would appreciate a week.
Just give me a week, two weeks?
Two weeks, you'll give me two weeks?
We have things coming up I promise.
No I'm, come on, you know me.
You know me, yeah?
Can you?
Ok, yes, no I hear you, I hear you.
So a week, you'll give me one week?
Ok? Ok.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
Bye.
Fuck.
Good morning.
- Morning.
You two sleeping together now,
and burning my toast?
Yeah I burnt your toast, sorry.
Strictly platonic I can assure you.
Sleeping together, burning my toast.
I'm sorry.
He's burnt like four pieces now.
No, only two.
You ate the other two.
No I didn't.
- I'm fucking tired,
didn't sleep at all.
Wine for breakfast?
It's better than burnt toast.
I'm Luka.
Of course, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- Doesn't it bother
you watching us working
while doing nothing?
- You call that working?
- Fuck you!
- This is my bed, you
wanna sleep downstairs?
No, no, no.
French boy, full of mystery huh?
That's fine.
I don't know, I just feel,
I feel like I could
tell you anything right?
I haven't really been able
to trust people very often
but you're easy to talk to you know?
I feel like you're listening.
You're listening.
I feel like you care.
We're not so different you know?
Um, when I first saw
you, I thought you were
just some asshole kid but I don't know,
there's just something about you.
I think I love you.
You're a good guy.
- You wanna make sure
the audience can see it.
Ok and I want you to
give me your best shot,
into here ok?
What are you gonna do a straight punch?
- Yep.
- Awesome.
Here we go, thank you Johnny.
Here we go.
Ready, you're gonna give me the eye.
I'm ready, ok.
Take a step back.
Right, one more, and really really pound
that shit into my fuckin' gut.
Hit me!
Oh fuck, gawd, I hate you
so much fucking racism.
Homophobia.
Hold it down.
I'm gonna beat homophobia into the past.
Argh, I hate you homophobia!
Come on, it's the beach.
Oh, get off, I'm wet!
Stop, stop.
So where's France?
Is it there?
Man, I don't know.
Is it over there?
No.
I don't know where it is.
It's straight through.
I don't care.
- Do you miss it?
- No.
- Well I'll move my
knight from here to here.
- Ok.
- Your turn.
I'll move my pawn here.
Mmm, and my knight here.
My knight here.
I ate your pawn.
- You ate it?
- Yep.
- You ate my pawn?
- You captured my pawn.
- No I ate it.
You didn't eat it.
Ok, all right, well
I'll move my knight here.
- Hmm, I move
my bishop...
Freddy.
How are you?
- How are you?
- I'm good, I'm good,
what are you doing here?
- I live here. -
- You live here?
Yeah, like down the block.
Oh my god, um this is Maurice.
Hi, how are you, I'm Freddy.
Yeah what are you up to tonight?
Nothing, what are you doing tonight?
Well, you know, sittin'.
- So nothing?
- Yep.
We're playing chess.
- Who's winning?
- - I am.
It's your turn,
- I'll take my unicorn
from here to maybe here.
That's cool, sounds good.
- I think that
wins. - - Yeah.
I think unicorns win.
There's no fighting with a unicorn.
- No. - -
Checkmate.
Good game, good job.
Thank you, thank you.
Come on ladies.
- Excusé moi.
- Excuse me.
Ladies? Thank you.
Hey Luka you can go babe.
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm, we got it.
Ok.
Betty what the fuck are you doing?
Having a drink.
- You're not supposed
to drink when you work,
you know that.
No one's here right now.
You've been drinking all fucking night.
People were there and they wanted
me to drink with them.
- This isn't a fucking party,
this is a business to be run.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
Yes, you understand that that's why
you're fucked up right now?
How much did we make tonight?
Let me see.
Are you fucking kidding me?
This is how much we have?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry.
You know earlier tonight we
had 200 more dollars in there?
You know that?
- No.
You know we're losing this bar
every fucking dollar it's making?
- I don't care about the
bar, I'm worried about you.
No get away from me.
Get away from me.
Everything's not ok right now.
You need to go upstairs and go to bed.
Now.
Now!
Fine, I'm going, I'm going.
Will you come with me?
- Just fucking go, I'm not
fucking coming with you.
Go!
- I'm going, I'm going.
Come on, give me one.
Give me one right on the chin, come on.
Come on, come on.
Talking dirty.
Come on you bitch, come on, come on.
Come on, come on bitch.
Come in harder.
You going light on me?
You sleeping on me?
Come on you guys.
You're fucking taller than me.
- All right, if anything
bad happens have you got him?
Yeah.
- I can give you a
free lesson if you want.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Ok.
- Come by next week.
I've trained a couple of people.
- Ok.
- Just my friends though.
Just friends?
- So it's special, you
should feel special.
Oh ok, I do feel special.
Why don't you come boxing pretty boy?
I'd be eaten alive.
They don't like my kind over there.
They'll get used to you.
He's laughing at you.
Yeah he is, fuck you.
- I think you need a
couple more lessons.
- So you work here?
- I do.
Why are you here on your day off?
I live upstairs too.
- Makes sense.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- I like it.
They're really nice, Kim and Betty.
They own the bar.
- I don't know them,
I just know Maurice.
Oh.
Got it from boxing, we share towels.
Oh do you?
I bet.
Are you even gay?
No, not at all.
Ok.
- I like girls, and
you look like a girl.
Thank you.
So you'll just do anything
that looks like a girl?
I'll do anything that moves.
I move.
Luka.
All right.
This is my bedroom.
This is my bed.
Is that what you want?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Huh?
Fine, don't say anything.
This is what you wanted right?
Huh?
So I slept with Charlie, big deal.
Can you leave?
Shut the fuck up.
- It was your idea to
begin with you know.
You said you just wanna be friends.
Can you please leave?
Happy?
Can you tell me what you want?
Anything, say anything!
You know, I really thought, never mind.
Whatever.
- Who are you?
- Charlie
- oh Maurice's
friend, sorry. - - Ok.
Who are you?
Kim, the owner.
Kim the owner.
You don't have any jobs do you?
No not right now.
All right.
You know, you can leave your number
at the bar though if you want.
- Ok.
- What's your name again?
- Charlie.
- Charlie, ok.
- Thanks Kim.
- Yeah.
What is this?
It's a tattoo.
I see, but, "j'ai douleur. "
This is not French.
What do you mean?
I mean, this is wrong.
In French you will never
say, "j'ai douleur. "
You will say, don't know,
j'ai mal, je souffre,
but never, "j'ai douleur. "
- Great.
- - Why?
Why what?
Why, "j'ai douleur?"
- Why did I get it?
- Yeah, what happened?
Back when I lived in Florida,
I dated this guy for about four years
and then I found out
that he had been sleeping
with my best friend for about two years,
so I got the tattoo and
packed up all my things,
and I just moved to New York.
Stupid right?
No, it's full of sense.
Full of mystery.
It's ok right now.
Je ne pas douleur.
Everybody's got, "douleur. "
- Douleur.
Yeah you're right.
- You're a big freakin'
kid you know that?
Just a big child.
It's all right.
Give me your hand.
The other one.
Put it down on the stage.
Like this.
- Do you carry that knife
around with you everywhere?
Do you trust me?
I hardly know you.
Turn yourself.
Starting now, you can't look at my face
during the night anymore.
Community chest, all right.
Go to jail.
That's great.
I'll sell it to you for 500.
- No, I'm not buying your,
"get out of jail free card. "
I'm gonna get out my own way.
Oh, sexy like this.
Ah, move please, we're
playing "monopoly,"
this is serious.
- How do you live
with yourself Charlie?
- Oh, you're disgusting,
fuck you, move!
Don't touch me.
Move!
Charlie, we're trying to play.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Shh, do you hear that?
- Subway.
- Shh.
It's Luka's asshole screaming my name.
I'm not interested.
By the way, with two houses.
- 400, what?
- You owe me $450.
You guys are fuckin' boring.
I'm gonna go fuck.
Do what you do best.
Six, seven, eight.
Oh, I think I own that.
- Ah, no, no no no, I
was right here, on chance.
Do you even stop fucking things?
Go, go again.
Oh, "get out of jail free. "
It's nice.
Save it.
- Your
turn. - - Ok.
Never Luka, never.
This guy's crazy.
You're a fucking pig Charlie.
I never stop Luka.
One, two, three, four.
Hi you guys, how you doing?
Good, ok cool.
I have a little special
performance for you guys tonight.
A little song, a little ditty,
an old jazz standard called, "smile. "
So I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Oh my god, thank you.
No.
Ok.
Not looking, not looking.
Nightmare.
You Kim?
Guess the same thing.
What's going on?
The bar's closing.
We can't afford the rent any more.
Be turned into fucking
condos or something.
Be gone in a couple of
weeks, a month maybe.
Nobody knows.
It's ok.
Stop, what's wrong?
Tell me what's wrong.
Look at me, look at me!
What is it?
Talk to me.
Please.
Give me the knife.
Hey baby it's ok.
- Hey you guys I think
he needs to be left alone.
Let go.
Come on, look at us.
Hey, look at me.
It'll be fine all right.
All right?
Hey, you're gonna be fine.
There's nothing out there.
No-one's gonna hurt you.
Thank you.
Come on, you're a fuckin' boxer,
you're all right, come on.
Charlie he's freaked out.
I know.
Give him some space.
Merde! Merde, I knew it!
You fucked up!
What are you looking for?
Where is it?
I don't know.
What knife?
That little black one
you've been carrying around?
I need my fucking knife!
- What are you doing?
- Have you seen his knife?
- No I haven't, honey
calm down, it's ok.
Who knows, who knows?
I need it, where is it?
You do not need a knife.
- You took it, you
took it, who took it?
No seriously, seriously, it's ok.
Where is it?
- Look at me, it's ok,
we love you it's fine.
I need my knife.
You don't need a knife.
- It's gonna be
fine. - - Calm down.
I need it, I need it!
You don't need a knife.
I need the knife, I need it.
Does he need a knife?
You don't need a knife.
I've got a reason to.
You don't need a knife, calm down.
All right, just chill, all right.
It's ok baby.
- We told you there's
nothing wrong, all right.
There is something wrong.
You're fine ok.
Please stop.
Stop, stop it, stop it, stop.
Don't worry, tomorrow I'll get a car.
I know a place where no
one will ever find him.
- Luka.
- Yeah?
Tonight can look at my face.
I love you, you know that?
My name is Maurice.
I know I don't really exist.
I met people who love me.
I met people I loved.
But I was only here for a while.
Just for a little while.